Preliminary Guide to the Lisner Auditorium records, 1946-2005 RG0055
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Programs, ledgers, 1940-1999; RG0055 Series 48; 21 Linear feet (Box 2, Box 3, Box 14, Box 1, Box 6, Box 7, Box 4, Box 5, Box 10, Box 11, Box 8, Box 9, Box 12, Box 13)
  - Programs, 06/1993 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    "The Ecclesia" (2 copies); DC Bodybuilding Championships and the first annual MS. Fitness DC contest (2 copies); The Federal City Performing Arts Association "Live From Amsterdam!" (2 copies); Lisner at Noon Series "Martin Berkofsky Works of Franz Liszt" (2 copies); Annual Employee Award Ceremony (2 copies)
  - Program folder, 07/1993 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Programs, 08/1993 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    GWU Colonial Convocation (2 copies); National Education Center "Capital Hill Campus Commencement Ceremony" (2 copies); Nrityanjali presents "Poornima Gowda in Bharatnatya Recital (2 copies); The Dance Institute of Washington Summer Repertory Program (2 copies)
  - Programs, 09/1993 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    Personal Economic Summit '93 (2 copies); Korea in Washington (2 copies); Paco de Lucia Sextet (2 copies); The Colonnade Gallery; 2nd Annual Hungry for Music "An Evening of Music" (2 copies); TOUCH-The Organization for Universal Communal Harmony presents "Ustad Vilayat Khan: World Famous Sitar Player" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 10/1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    The Canadian Brass; Jinling Art Performance Troupe of China (2 copies); Washington Concert Opera (2 copies); The National Heritage Fellowships (2 copies); Joy of Motion Dance Center presents "A Celebration of Life" (2 copies); Washington Performing Arts Society American Indian Dance Theatre (2 copies)
  - Programs, 11/1993 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    The New Vic Theatre of London "Canterbury Tales" (2 copies); Washington Performing Arts Society presents "Karen Finley" (2 copies); Coors Extra Gold "Super Talent Show Case" (2 copies); Lisner At Noon series "Melissa Lesbines" (2 copies); University Symphonic Band Fall Concert (2 copies)
  - Programs, 12/1993 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    The Washington Revels presents "The Christmas Revels" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 02/1994 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Campus HI Lites (2 copies)
  - Programs, 03/1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    The Korean Student Association "Korean Friendship Night" (2 copies) & poster; Ladeco Chilean Airlines (2 copies)
  - Programs, 04/1994-06/1994 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    "Catch A Rising Star Follies" (2 copies); The Gay Men's Chorus of Washington "Our Show of Shows" (2 copies); The Samples in Concert poster; Noa and Gil Dor in Concert (2 copies); Washington Performing Arts Society and Charlin Jazz Society "Diz and Duke" (2 copies); Parade of the Arts "The Pan Masters Steel Orchestra" (2 copies); The Gay Men's Chorus of Washington D.C. and Los Angeles "Remember Stonewall" (2 copies)
  - Programs, 1995-1997 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Postcard of "GW & WWII: A University & the War Effort"; Washington Performing Arts Society Parade of the Artists "Duke Ellington Show Choir" (2 copies); Laurel Farrin (2 copies)
  - Programs, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Lisner At Noon "Heart and Soul: A Musical Look at Love"; Atlas of Modern Jewish History; 20th Anniversary Tour "Jesus Christ Superstar" (2 copies); Washington Performing Arts Society "Inti-Illimani Paco Pena John Williams (2 copies)
  - Programs, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Maya Angelou's "And Still I Rise" (2 copies); Bharatiya Vidya Bhavan, USA presents "Pankaj, Nirmal, & Manhar;" ICM Artists present "Mummenschanz Parade" (2 copies)
  - Programs, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Jose Greco; Pete Seeger; Tito Puente; National Chinese Opera Theater; Evening with Bobby Short; Hungarian Folk Dance; Itzhak Perlman; inti-illimani; Match Made in Heaven
- Programs, 2000; RG0055 Series 49; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series includes programs from July-December 2000.
  Formerly ACC#937
  - Yehoram Gaon, 02/11/1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Sponsor: Quali-teev Productions
  - Musica de las Americans 2000, 07/01/2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Opera International Il Tabarro and Gianni Schicchi, 08/04/2000-08/06/2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Sponsor: Opera International. 2 programs. Performances on Aug 4 and 6
  - Boka Ndeye and Dueka Ndor, 09/01/2000-09/02/2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Sponsor: KanKouran West African Dance Company. 3 programs
  - Induction Convocation, 09/11/2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sponsor: National Society of Collegiate Scholars. 2 programs
  - Opening Convocation, 09/12/2000 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Sponsor: University Special Events
  - Medical School Convocation, 09/15/2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Sponsor: GW Medical School. 2 programs
  - Rahat Nusrat Fateh Ali Khan, 09/24/2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Sponsor: Zee Gold and Asian Sounds; Amala Diallo
  - National Heritage Fellowship, 09/22/2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Sponsor: National Heritage Foundation
  - Yesudas and Chithra, 10/07/2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Sponsor: Indians for Music and Performing Arts. 1 poster
  - Janacek's Jenufa, 10/13/2000-10/15/2000 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Sponsor: Washington Concert Opera. 2 programs. Performances on Oct 13 and 15
  - President's Night (Preservation Hall Jazz Band), 10/19/2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Sponsor: University Special Events. 2 programs
  - The Legend of Tamar, 10/26/2000-10/29/2000 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Sponsor: Erisioni Productions. 2 programs and 2 posters. Performances on Oct 26 and 29
  - GW Department of Music, 11/02/2000 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Sponsor: GW Department of Music
  - Harvest of Harmony, 11/04/2000 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Sponsor: DC Chapter of the Barbershop Harmony Society. 2 programs
  - The New Voice of Fado Misia, 11/05/2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Sponsor: Lisner Auditorium. 2 programs
  - White Oak Dance Project, 11/10/2000-11/11/2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Shaolin Warriors, 11/17/2000-11/18/2000 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - American Youth Philharmonic, 11/19/2000 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    Sponsor: American Youth Philharmonic. 2 programs
  - University Symphony Orchestra, 11/20/2000 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    Sponsor: GW Department of Music. 2 programs
  - Christmas Revels, 12/01/2000-12/10/2000 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    Sponsor: Washington Revels. 1 poster and 1 program. Performances on Dec 1-3 and 8-10
- Office records, 1941-1990; RG0055 Series 50; 15 Linear feet (Box 10, Box 6, Box 7, Box 8, Box 9, Box 2, Box 3, Box 4, Box 5, Box 1)
  This series includes contracts/rental agreements, budget records, employee lists, news releases, correspondence (including Frank Early), appointment books, usher assignments (including show dates), operations documents, programs, pamphlets, photographs, tickets from events. The materials range in date from 1941-1990.
  Formerly ACC# 945
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 4001-4012, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 4013-4025, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 5001-5014, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 5015-5026, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 6001-6014, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 6015-6035, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 7001-7015, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 7016-7031, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 7033-7044, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 8001-8018, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 8019-8034, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 8035-8049, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 9001-9022, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 9023-9042, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 9043-9059, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 10001-10014, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 10015-10031, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 10032-10045, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 11001-11012, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 11013-11027, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 11029-11048, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 12001-12019, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 12020-12034, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 12035-12054, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 13002-13022, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 13023-13044, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 13045-13065, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 14001-14017, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 14018-14029, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 14030-14041, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 15001-15016, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 15017-15033, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 15034-15042, 1977-1982 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 16001-16019, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 16020-16042, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 17001-17017, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 17018-17033, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 17034-17050, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 18001-18022, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 18023-18052, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 19001-19024, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 19025-19058, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 20004-20020, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 20021-20036, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Lisner Auditorium-contracts, 20037-20056, 1982-1987 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts, 63001-65001, 1963-1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts, 01/27/1963-01/21/1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Completed contracts, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts and Applications, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts, 01/26/1966-02/12/1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Contracts, The American Light Opera Company, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Administrative Management Plan, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Auditorium Carpeting, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Auditorium Lighting, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Auditorium Seating, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Auditorium Seating-numbering, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Background info. regarding National Ballet, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Bills, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Budget Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Dance, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Employee Lists, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Expense Account, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Grumman, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - International Students Society, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Letters, Department Memos, Newsletters, 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Lisner Auditorium goals and objectives, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - News releases for Lisner events, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Opera Society of Washington, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Opera Society of Washington, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Payroll Sheets, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Roscoe Laboratories, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1948-1953 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Schedules of Events-"Do you Know?", 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Shrader Manufacturing Company, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Sound Equipment, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Special Events, Attractions, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Stage Equipment Catalogues, 1940 ca. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Stores Department, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Tentative Schedules, correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Theatre Equipment, (Faerber), 1946-1949 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Theatre Supplies Equipment, 1941-1942 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Theatre Supplies Equipment, 1950-1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Air Force Officer's Wives Club of D.C., 1959 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - American Medical Association, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Annandale High School, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bernice Hammond School of Dance, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Chevrolet, 1950-1956 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Chevrolet, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Children's House, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Christmas Pageant and Peace, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Coppieus, Schang, and Brown, Inc., (Division of Columbia Arts Management, Inc.), 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - D.C. Recreation Department, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Denied Applications, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Development Corporation for Israel, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Fall Concert-Seating plan, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Falls Church High School, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Friday Morning Music Club, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Future Engagements, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Harvard Club of Washington, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Hayes Concert Corporation, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Indiana Society, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1957-1959 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - International Cultural Exchange, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - International Night, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - John Dildine, 1952-1958 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Langstaff, John, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Latter Day Saints, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Leon Fokine/Marion Venable, 1951-1958 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Leventhal, Harold, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Lincoln Memorial Congregational Temple, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Lutheran Action Council, 1952-1958 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - McLean High School, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Music Educators National Conference, NEA Center, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - National Ballet Society, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - National Council of Jewish Women D.C. Section, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - National Council of Jewish Women Washington, D.C. Section, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - National Cultural Foundation, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - National Folk Festival, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - National Folk Festival, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - National Grange, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - National Society of Arts and Letters, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - National Symphony of Washington, 1967-1970 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - National Symphony Orchestra, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - National Symphony, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - National Symphony, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - National Symphony, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - National Symphony, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - New York Ave. Presbyterian Church, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Northeast Academy of Dance, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Ohio State University Alumni Club of Washington, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Opera Society of Washington, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Paid bills, 1950-1956 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Parent and Child Inc., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Patrick Hayes, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Philippines Embassy, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Philosophical Society, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Plymouth Congregational Church, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - President's People to People Program, Music Committee, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Princeton Club of Washington, 1956-1958 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Psi Chi, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Retail, WDS Union, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Saint Sophia Greek Orthodox Cathedral, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - St. Ann's Church and School, 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - St. George's Church, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Warner School of Dance, 1951-1959 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Washington Ballet Guild, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Washington Opera Society, 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Washington School of Ballet, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Yale Club of Washington, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Yale Glee Club, 1951-1958 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Yenching University, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Air Force Officers' Wives Club, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Air Force Officers and Wives Club, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Alpha Kappa Alpha, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - America-Israel Cultural Foundation, Inc., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Arch Diocese of Washington, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trade, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Christian Endeavor Society, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Church of St. Timothy, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Civic Ballet Society of D.C., 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Colonial Program, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Columbia Artists Management Inc., 1953-1959 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Convocation and Baccalaureate, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Dartmouth Club of Washington, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Delta Sigma Theta Sorority Washington Alumni Chapter, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Dunbarton College of Holy Cross, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Engineer Alumni Association, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Folk Music Guild, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Friday Morning Music Club, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - G.W. Folk Music Society, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Hurok Attractions with Patrick Hayes, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Institute of Contemporary Arts, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Jeb Stuart High School, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Jones-Haywood, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - Latter Day Saints, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - March of Dimes Telethon, 1969-1960 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Metropolitan Civic Ballet of Maryland, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Montana Central Train, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - Montgomery County Arts Center-Mr. Harold Boxer, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - Moral Re-Armament, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Mortar Board, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Mount Vernon Seminary, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Music-Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - National Folk Festival, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - National Negro Opera Foundation, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - National Symphony, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - New York City Opera Company, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Oberlin Orchestra and College, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Opera Society of Washington, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Pan American Union, 1948-1958 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Past Shows, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Patrick Hayes, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - People to People, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - People's Congregational, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Beta Chapter, The National Sorority of Phi Delta Kappa, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Phi Sigma Kappa, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Pick and Hammer Club of Washington, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Princeton Club of Washington, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Princeton Club of Washington, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Princeton Club, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Program Schedule, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - S.P.E.B.S.Q.S.A., 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Salvation Army, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 71)
  - Society for Personnel Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - Southeast Neighborhood House, 1960-1963 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - The Big Sisters of D.C., Inc., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - The Friday Morning Music Club, Inc., of Washington, D.C., 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Third International Congress of Plastic Surgery, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - Time for Defense Broadcasts, 1949-1950 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - Tyser, Russ, 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - Unesco, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - United States Air Force, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - Washington Ballet Guild, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - Washington Ballet Guild, 1958-1960 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - Washington Home for Foundlings, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - Washington Hospital Center School of Nursing, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 84)
  - Yale Club of Washington D.C., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 85)
  - Yale Club, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 86)
  - Yale University, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 87)
  - Record Album-Spotlight Outstanding Solo Performances, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Record Album-The U.S. Air Force Symphony Orchestra, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Record Album-Little Feat-Waiting for Columbus, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Guests Signature Book for the "Lisner Auditorium-42 years of Service" Memorabilia of moments Exhibition, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Photo Album-Lisner At Noon, April 27, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Video Tape-Show times-Tommy Davidson Show, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Appointment book, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Appointment book, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Appointment book, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Appointment book, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Appointment book, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Appointment book, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Appointment book, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Various Appointment books, 1969-1990 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dance Students in LCN-photos and negatives, 04/13/1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Lisner Auditorium-photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Lisner Auditorium-photos, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lisner Log book, 1968-1972 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Lisner Plan book, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Opening Reception of "Lisner Auditorium-42 years of Service" at the Colonade Gallery, 06/07/1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - The New Book-Scheduling Events, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - University Band Fall Concert-Ben Fritz Director, 11/1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Vietnamese Association in Washington, DC
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Radio City Music Hall-Troubadours
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Ballet Spectacular
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    Best Music On and Off Campus, Friday Morning Music Club Concerts, National Symphony
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1964 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    The National Ballet, Friday Morning Music Club Concerts
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    National Symphony, Friday Morning Music Club Concerts
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    The Art of Engineering or The Facts of Life, Society for Personnel Administration Fifth Annual Conference on Automation And Personnel Administration, Washington Performing Arts Society, Look Homeward, Angel, Interfraternity Council Panhellenic Association
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    GWU Awards Dinner, All Request Program, The Nutcracker, The Challenge of Leadership
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Washington Performing Arts Society
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    The Johann Sebastian Bach International Competitions, The Oratorio Society, The Charles H. Tompkins Memorial Lecture in Surgery, Enrico Macias, The Kinetic Art Film Series
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Nikolais Dance Theatre, Two Faces of India, Ida Kaminska, Big Sis Fashion Show, Nana Mouskouri, The Al Huang Dance Concert
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Embassy of the Argentine Republic, GWU School of Medicine Opening Assembly, The Believers, Charlie Byrd in Concert, Sallah
  - Lisner Auditorium-Pamphlets, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 21)